netserveafrica.com 2009-04-22

# NetServeAfrica Support

|  | 

|  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
|  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
|  |   
  
  | 

NetServeAfrica takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how NetServeAfrica treats personal information that NetServeAfrica collects and receives, including information related to your past use of NetServeAfrica products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that NetServeAfrica does not own or control, or to people that NetServeAfrica does not employ or manage. In addition, certain NetServeAfrica associated companies have their own privacy statements. 

**Information Collection and Use**

      **General**

  * NetServeAfrica collects personal information when you register with NetServeAfrica, when you use NetServeAfrica products or services, when you visit NetServeAfrica pages or the pages of certain NetServeAfrica partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. NetServeAfrica may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address and information about your assets. Once you register with NetServeAfrica and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * NetServeAfrica collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer. 
  * NetServeAfrica automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, NetServeAfrica cookie information, and the page you request. 
  * NetServeAfrica uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfil your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

      **Children**

  * NetServeAfrica will not contact children under age 15 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. 
  * NetServeAfrica does not ask a child under age 15 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * NetServeAfrica does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with NetServeAfrica under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help NetServeAfrica communicate with you about offers from NetServeAfrica and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of NetServeAfrica's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if NetServeAfrica is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, NetServeAfrica will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * NetServeAfrica displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 
    * NetServeAfrica does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
    * NetServeAfrica advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 
  * NetServeAfrica works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. For more information regarding providers of products or services that you've requested please read our detailed reference links. 

**Cookies**

  * NetServeAfrica may set and access NetServeAfrica cookies on your computer. 
  * NetServeAfrica lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to NetServeAfrica 's cookies. 
  * NetServeAfrica uses web beacons to access NetServeAfrica cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with NetServeAfrica products and services. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

      **General**

  * You can edit your NetServeAfrica Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. 
  * New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the NetServeAfrica service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the NetServeAfrica Newsletter, that are considered part of your NetServeAfrica account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 
  * You can delete your NetServeAfrica account by visiting our Account Deletion page. Please note that some information that might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with relevant regulations to protect personal information about you. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * NetServeAfrica may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your NetServeAfrica account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us at privacy@netserveafrica.com. 

Effective Date: January 01, 2006 

|    
| 

|   
  
|
